<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Unzip</string>
    <string name="tv_title_on_boarding">Welcome to UnZip!</string>
    <string name="tv_intro">Unzip can extract ZIP, RAR, 7Z, TAR and all other compressed files. Supports split archives for certain formats.</string>
    <string name="btn_get_start">Get started!</string>
    <string name="tv_internal_storage">Internal Storage</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="Compressed">Compressed</string>
    <string name="Compressing">Compressing</string>
    <string name="extracted">Extracted</string>
    <string name="file_explorer">File Explorer</string>
    <string name="google_driver">Google Driver</string>
    <string name="dropbox">Dropbox</string>
    <string name="recently">Recently</string>
    <string name="see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="recycle_bin">Recycle Bin</string>
    <string name="setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="show_recently">Show Recently</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="privavy_policy">Privavy Policy</string>
    <string name="term">Term of Use</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="shareApp">Share This App</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="review">Write a review</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="no_files_found">NO FILES FOUND</string>
    <string name="open_permission">Open setting permissions</string>
    <string name="guideTurnOnPermission" translatable="false"><![CDATA[Please turn on permission at [Setting] > [Permission]]]></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="rotating">Rotating</string>
    <string name="detail">Detail</string>
    <string name="tv_recycle_bin">Recycle Bin</string>
    <string name="delete_notify">"Files will be delete forever. "</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="restock">Restock</string>
    <string name="restore_notify">Are you sure to restock this file?</string>
    <string name="rename">Rename</string>
    <string name="move_recycle_bin_notify">Move file to Recycle Bin?</string>
    <string name="delete_permanently">Delete permanently</string>
    <string name="term_content" translatable="false">
        <![CDATA[ <p><strong>Terms of Use</strong></p>
        <p>If you continue to use this application , you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by
            the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern
            app relationship with you in relation to this application. If you disagree with any part
            of these terms and conditions, please do not use our application.</p>


        <p>This is a security service and we do not guarantee to give you %100 security. It was
            designed to protect your conversations and having them backed up on encrypted cloud
            platform. You accept that we do not guarantee to give you exact results by downloading
            and upgrading your membership. Keep in mind that this app does not add a passcode to the
            original applications, only the imported conversations of your choice.</p>


        <p><strong>Links To Other Web Sites</strong><br> We have no control over, and assumes no
            responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web
            sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that Ontrack SUNTECH LTD. shall not
            be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or
            alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content,
            goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services. We strongly
            advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third party web
            sites or services that you visit.</p>


        <p><strong>Law</strong><br> These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding
            our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have between us
            regarding the Service.</p>


        <p><strong>Changes</strong><br> We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or
            replace these Terms at any time. Any changes to the Terms will be effective immediately.
            By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become effective, you
            agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please
            stop using the Service.</p>


        <p><strong>Warranty Disclaimer</strong><br> This is an unofficial product. Any product
            names, logos, brands, and other trademarks or images featured or referred to within this
            app are the property of their respective trademark holders. Any of these trademark
            holders are not affiliated This is app, our products, or with us. They do not sponsor or
            endorse this app or any of our online products. Neither we nor any third parties provide
            any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or
            suitability of the information and materials found or offered in this app for any
            particular purpose.<br> Your use of any information or materials in this app is entirely
            at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility
            to ensure that any products, services or information available through this app meet
            your specific requirements.</p>


        <p><strong>Free Trial</strong> <br>Suntech provides a FREE TRIAL period during which you can
            use all features of the service for a limited period of time. You can manage or cancel
            the trial subscription through your App Store account. </p>


        <p><strong>Payment</strong><br> We services are provided through the APP STORE on a
            paid subscription basis. We rates for services are listed in the App and on the App
            Store. We reserves the right to modify its rates at any time and/or to offer
            special promotions. We does not issue refunds for services. We does not send
            invoices to its customers. Instead, you have confidential access to your account balance
            information through the App Store. If you have a billing dispute, you must contact the
            App Store to seek a remedy. </p>


        <p><strong>Contact us</strong><br> If you have questions regarding this privacy policy, you
            may email suntectltd.software@gmail.com<br> Phone number: 0353358792<br> Room 601, Lot
            B12D21, Cau Giay New Urban Area, Dich Vong Hau Ward, Cau Giay, Hanoi</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="policy_content" translatable="false">
        <![CDATA[ <p><strong>Privacy Policy</strong></p>

        <p>Your privacy is important to Our App Service. Our Privacy Policy covers how we collect,
        use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. We hope our policy is straightforward
        and easy-to-understand. Please take a minute to review the details of our privacy practices
        below.</p>

        <p><strong>How We Collect Information</strong><br>
        We collect information in order to provide you with better, higher-quality, and more
        personalized services. We collect information by the following means:<br>
        1. When you use our email support services, we collect your correspondence in order to
        build up a public knowledge base, which will be available to all users of the site. Your
        correspondence will most likely not be used verbatim, but paraphrased in an FAQ format.<br>
        2. The data we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us, the choices you
        make, including your privacy settings, and the products and features you use. The data we
        collect can include SDK/API/JS code version, browser, Internet service provider, IP
        address, platform, timestamp, application identifier, application version, application
        distribution channel, independent device identifier, Android ad master identifier, network
        card (MAC) address, and international mobile device identification code(IMEI/android
        ID/IDFA/OPENUDID/GUID, SIM card IMSI information)to provide statistical analysis services,
        and the accuracy of report data is calibrated by geographic location to provide basic
        anti-cheating capabilities. The equipment model, the terminal manufacturer, the terminal
        device operating system version, the session start/stop time, the location of the language,
        the time zone and the network state (WiFi and so on), the hard disk, the CPU, and the
        battery use, etc.
        </p>

        <p><strong>How We Use Information</strong><br>
        We use the information collected through this app product: (I) to communicate with you;
        (II) to process your requests and transactions; (III) to improve the app; (IV) to customize
        the services and/or products we provide to you; (V) to assist with our product and service
        development; (VI) to perform marketing analysis; and (VII) for other purposes related to
        our business.<br>
        Our product integrates Youmeng+ SDK to provide statistical analysis services and calibrate
        the accuracy of report data through geographic location to provide basic anti-cheating
        capabilities.
        </p>

        <p><strong>Third party accounts</strong><br>
        Our App Service does not store any other third part service passwords. Your account
        information is not disclosed to this app and you are free to cancel any of your social
        networking website connections with this app at any time.
        </p>

        <p><strong>Sharing of personal data</strong><br>
        To improve our product and provide you better service, we also share personal data with
        vendors or agents working on our behalf for the purposes described in this privacy policy.
        For example, companies we&#39;ve hired to provide data analytical services may need collect
        and access to personal data to provide those functions. In such cases, these companies must
        abide by our data privacy and security requirements.
        </p>

        <p><strong>Legal basis for data processing</strong><br>
        We process Personal Data for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, as described
        above. Our legal basis to process personal data includes processing that is: necessary for
        the performance of the contract with you (for example, to provide you with the services you
        request and to identify and authenticate you so you may use the Sites); necessary to comply
        with legal requirements (for example, to comply with applicable accounting rules and to
        make mandatory disclosures to law enforcement); necessary for our legitimate interests (for
        example, to manage our relationship with you, to ensure the security of our services, to
        communicate with you about our products and services); and based on consent by our
        customers (for example, to place certain cookies and to share your information with third
        parties for advertising purposes).<br>
        In some instances, you may be required to provide us with Personal Data for processing as
        described above, in order for us to be able to provide you all of our services, and for you
        to use all the features of our App.
        </p>

        <p><strong>International transfers of personal data</strong><br>
        Our business may require us to transfer your Personal Data to countries outside of the
        European Economic Area (&#34;EEA&#34;), including to countries such as the People&#39;s
        Republic of China or Singapore. We take appropriate steps to ensure that recipients of your
        Personal Data are bound to duties of confidentiality and we implement measures such as
        standard contractual clauses. A copy of those clauses can be obtained by contacting our
        Help Center.
        </p>

        <p><strong>Your rights</strong><br>
        Subject to limitations in applicable law, you are entitled to object to or request the
        restriction of processing of your Personal Data, and to request access to, rectification,
        erasure and portability of your own Personal Data.<br>
        Where the use of your information is based on consent, you can withdraw this consent at any
        time without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its
        withdrawal.<br>
        Requests should be submitted by contacting us through our developer account e-Mail on
        Google Play.<br>
        If you are aware of changes or inaccuracies in your information, you should inform us of
        such changes so that our records may be updated or corrected. You may lodge a complaint
        with a supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of your Personal Data
        infringes applicable law.<br>
        We retain your Personal Data as long as needed to provide services or products to you, or
        as required or permitted by applicable laws, such as tax and accounting laws.
        </p>

        <p><strong>Transparency and Choice</strong><br>
        You can also control which social websites you wish to share or upload.
        </p>

        <p><strong>Changes</strong><br>
        Our Privacy Policy may change occasionally. We will not reduce your rights under this
        Privacy Policy without providing explicit, advance notice. We will post any privacy policy
        changes on this page and, in the event of significant changes, we will provide a more
        prominent notice (such as an email notification).<br>
        If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.
        </p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tv_file_name">Name</string>
    <string name="tv_file_path">Path</string>
    <string name="tv_file_size">Size</string>
    <string name="tv_file_modification_date">Modification date</string>
    <string name="tv_file_resolution">Resolution</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="slash_symbol" translatable="false">/</string>
    <string name="extract">Extract</string>
    <string name="edit_name">Name…</string>
    <string name="tv_pass_word">Password</string>
    <string name="edit_pass_word">Please enter if your file has a password</string>
    <string name="clearAll">Clear all</string>
    <string name="export">Export</string>
    <string name="internal_storage">Internal storage</string>
    <string name="explorer">File explorer</string>
    <string name="file_name">File name</string>
    <string name="file_password">Password</string>
    <string name="archive_fromat">Archive format</string>
    <string name="six_items">6 items</string>
    <string name="image">Image</string>
    <string name="video" translatable="false">Video</string>
    <string name="audio">Audio</string>
    <string name="document">Document</string>
    <string name="download">Download</string>
    <string name="apk" translatable="false">Apk</string>
    <string name="btn_add_account">Add account</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Enter the name of the file or folder you want to search for…</string>
    <string name="zip" translatable="false">Zip</string>
    <string name="rar" translatable="false">Rar</string>
    <string name="seven_z" translatable="false">.7z</string>
    <string name="tar" translatable="false">Tar</string>
    <string name="doc" translatable="false">Doc</string>
    <string name="pdf" translatable="false">PDF</string>
    <string name="pptx" translatable="false">PowerPoint</string>
    <string name="excel" translatable="false">Excel</string>
    <string name="txt" translatable="false">Txt</string>
    <string name="accept_replace">Replace the file in the destination</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip this file</string>
    <string name="tv_restore_title">Replace or Skip Files</string>
    <string name="select">Select</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="all">All</string>
    <string name="install_notify">The app is being installed</string>
    <string name="install_result">The application has been installed successfully</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="tv_alert">Currently, we only support Zip files with passwords, please choose the .zip format to support Zip files with passwords.</string>
    <string name="progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="cannot_read_file">Sorry, Unzip can\'t read this file</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="name">Name…</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="wifi_transfer" translatable="false">Wifi transfer</string>
    <string name="textAlertwftransferoff">Please turn in the button to work</string>
    <string name="textAlertwftransferwfoff">Please make sure that you are connected to Wifi</string>
    <string name="textAlertwftransferon">Copy and paste the following URL into your FTP Client or Windows file explorer</string>
    <string name="alert_signOutDropbox">Do you want to sign out of DropBox?</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="file_selceted">You have just selected</string>
    <string name="tv_fileselected">Open to the folder you need, then press \'Upload\'</string>
    <string name="file">file</string>
    <string name="alert_change_lang">Select Languages</string>
    <string name="Eng">English</string>
    <string name="vn">Vienamese</string>
    <string name="alert_changelang">Select Languages</string>
    <string name="upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="change_lanng">English</string>
    <string name="item">item</string>
    <string name="items">items</string>
    <string name="google_drive_notify">This feature will now be updated in the near future. We are very sorry for this inconvenience</string>
</resources>